
const quizApi = [
{
 "question":"who founded Nigera's first political party ?",
  "possibleAnswers":['samuel nduka','baba ojo','chiakonam sure','udechukwu','ude','chinazaa onah','obinna eze','sylvester ugwu'],
  "correctAnswer":"herbert macaulay",
  "name":"quiz"
},
{
 "question":"which is the nigeria state with the lagest land mass ?",
  "possibleAnswers":['enugu state','ebonyi state','anambra state',"imo state",'kaduna state','lagos state','jigawa state','benue state'],
  "correctAnswer":"niger",
  "name":"quiz"
},
{
 "question":"what's my wife name ?",
  "possibleAnswers":['enugu state','ebonyi state','anambra state',"imo state",'kaduna state','lagos state','jigawa state','benue state'],
  "correctAnswer":"mary",
  "name":"quiz"
},
{
 "question":"which is the nigeria state has 'light if the nation' as her slogan ?",
  "possibleAnswers":['enugu state','ebonyi state','anambra state',"imo state",'kaduna state','lagos state','jigawa state','benue state'],
  "correctAnswer":"anambra state",
  "name":"quiz"
},
{
 "question":"what's is the largest moutain in the world ? ",
  "possibleAnswers":['kilimanjaro','odogwu mountain','hilltop',"congo",'morocco mountain'],
  "correctAnswer":"moutain everest",
  "name":"quiz"
},
{
 "question":"which state in nigeria is famous for blacksmith works ?",
  "possibleAnswers":['enugu state','ebonyi state','anambra state',"imo state",'kaduna state','lagos state','jigawa state','benue state'],
  "correctAnswer":"anambra state",
  "name":"quiz"
},
{
 "question":"which state in nigeria is famous for blacksmith works ?",
  "possibleAnswers":['enugu state','ebonyi state','anambra state',"imo state",'kaduna state','lagos state','jigawa state','benue state'],
  "correctAnswer":"anambra state",
  "name":"quiz"
},
{
 "question":"where is headquaters of ECOWAS ?",
  "possibleAnswers":['enugu state','ebonyi state','anambra state',"imo state",'kaduna state','lagos state','jigawa state','benue state'],
  "correctAnswer":"abuja",
  "name":"quiz"
},
{
 "question":"which country first won the world cup ?",
  "possibleAnswers":['russia','nigeria','egypt',"australlia",'united kingdom','china','burkinafaso','tazania','italy'],
  "correctAnswer":"uruguay",
  "name":"quiz"
},
{
 "question":"how states are in northern nigeria ?",
  "possibleAnswers":['24','21','15',"17",'28','29','','9'],
  "correctAnswer":"19",
  "name":"quiz"
},
{
 "question":"how states are in southern nigeria ?",
  "possibleAnswers":['24','21','15','28','29','','9'],
  "correctAnswer":"17",
  "name":"quiz"
}
];